GARDA ARRANIRI

Software Engineer

Deli Serdang, Sumatera Utara Phone: +628153132912

Email: garda.arraniri@gmail.com



SUMMARY

I am Garda, graduated as Information Technology Program in University of Sumatera Utara. A solo Fullstack Developer with less than 1 year of experience who have passion for creating digital stuff. I love to keep up with the evolution around web technology development. Familiar with application development especially web development. Proven to have developed personal projects as well as clients project (look at portofolio section).

EXPERIENCES

Solo Full-Stack Developer - Deli Serdang, Indonesia

(April 2021 - Present)

- Developed and designing applications based on Business Requirements Document (BRD).
- Created API Specification and integrating the API based on UI/UX.

Digital Talent Scholarship - Medan, Indonesia

Cybersecurity Class (July 2019 – Agustus 2019)

- Learned the fundamental practice of Cyber Operations.
- Analyzed and mitigated types of cyber attack on Cyber Security

EDUCATION

University Of Sumatera Utara (2014-2021)

Bachelor of Information Technology - GPA 3.28

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office : Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Power Point

Database Operation: MySql, MongoDb

Programming : HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, NodeJS, ReactJS

ESSAY

Implementation of K-Prototype Algorithm in Motor Vehicle Market Segmentation based on Credit Characteristic.

PORTOFOLIO

Visit: http://www.arranworks.com